export const DESKTOP_WIDTH = 1280;

export const TABLET_WIDTH = 768;

export const MOBILE_WIDTH = 480;

export const initialQuestions = [
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'A few years ago, the basketball player Marcus Morris had a son. After that, Morris added to his playing kit… what did he add on his kit?', 
    answer: 'Sr.',
    hint: 'His son - Marcus Morris, Jr.'
  },
  { 
    question: 'In the trailer for Wolfenstein: The New Order, you can see Germans crossing the street, a Nazi flag is in an unusual place, and a soldier on a European city square... Doing what?', 
    answer: 'Kissing a girl',
    hint: 'This is a game in the genre of alternative history. Episodes of the trailer refer to famous photographs: only instead of the Beatles, the Germans cross Abbey Road, the flag is on the moon, and the soldier of the victorious side, being not in Times Square, but in Paris Square, kisses an unfamiliar girl.'
  },
];